All right good afternoon.
We're going to start right on time.
I hope you're enjoying build so far...I heard something interesting in
the keynote this morning that I thought was in the resonated with me and
...resend now is it's never been a better time to be a developer it's never been
That seems so very true I want
...really quickly with the question how many people in here believe they're building
...to build a successful application successful application really popular and
...only raising your hand right...right it's
...only reason I'm a quote.
If you are successful.
Enterprise customers will require new to integrate
...application with our enterprise identity management system enterprises
rely on these identity management systems to do things like control access control with
...very important assets that they invest in deeply and if you
build a successful application that's meaningful for that company or that organization your
...going to ask and integrate...anybody...this...comes from
by the way actually I descent so totally...here first all you can say
hundred-percent because I work for microsoft and I work on active directory I'm going to end
...slightly you might have...you may...your customers that active
...is a very popular part of enterprise on any management systems and people actually want
you to integrate when active directory so if you're successfully one-in-eight
...with active directory mining store...manager in the as our active directory
team we've been working on a capability that we call identity management as a service
otherwise known as an interactive directory I'm going to talk to-you today about how integrating when
...active directory integrates you with active directory in fact makes
that much simpler than it used...in the past especially if you're
...application...building a mobile application how do you how do you integrate when
your customer asks you this I'm going to show you a...very-high-level how you can do that and some of the
benefits that you can get from doing this integration not only by making things simpler
easier for your customer but also we can help you promote your application
...active directory answer active directory and with office three
sixty five so we'll go through what is identity management as a service and how does it change the name
...talk about some of these benefits that you can...do a little demo how to integrate I'm not going to go
...super...staff there's a couple of other sessions or
...three other sessions here and build where you...get much more detail...has a couple of
...building web apps...building...mobile applications mandel also has a
...specifically on I tips...troubleshooting but
we'll go very-high-level here to give you an idea...what the integration I tanks and then we'll look at
through the future things so what we're doing right now as a as a way point
and watch longer journey there's...of really interesting stuff that we're doing...identity at microsoft?
All right let's begin.
By talking
about what does it take to integrate today with active directory
...enterprise identity management system typically when a customer comes and
...asking for a couple things first...one federation and that's not just because they
one single...on for their end-users but it's also because they want when
they're users aren't disabled in their identity management system on
premises they want them to looms access to your application if you have a separate user accounts
...your operation then they're not going to remember to go...disable them and stuff like that
...federation they don't have to worry about that the second thing that's often a
challenge for you is you might need to know when the user awry is...
user operation before they for sign-in maybe just-in-time...in your application
through federation might not enough for you might need to know more details about the user then you get
...might need to know information about the groups there any
...where they...organizational hierarchy or other kinds of details that
euros the northern forced to have your customer give you some...any
...probably...where you havepart of your management consul the customer up loans
...xcel file or something with details...they...components or you have
...api that they call and they're constantly calling...is more work for
you and for your customer when they one-on-one in your system in
fact today without identity...service how does identity management
is a service change the dynamic here well what we're going
to do is we're going to bring the identity management system to the cloud and when
we bring into the cloud a couple of very important things are going to happen number-one
your application...now depending on a very consistent interface
content at identity management data both and...the directly which you probably
...even...the past unless you make special arrangements with your customer to be able to
...in...without oper something down into their own consist directory now the directly
...in the cloud where you can get at it you can query and you can even
manipulative and setting up federation is no longer
a complicated exercise with the exchange...someone
...parameters that you might do with one of your support engineers over the phone or
that-you might have built a self-service application for but often setting up federation is just
not an easy task and, what we're going what we're doing is making it so you can programmatic
re-establish the...sign on relationship...the customer and all that customers
...one-click and consenting to using
...application we'll see that in the demo the other thing that we do have identity management
as a services we create essential connectivity between...on premises and then
in management systems that these organizations have been building over the last couple
of decades and we are provided way to get that information up in
...cloud regardless of what they might be running on premises and this is
a particular challenge for us is microsoft because weekly?
Is connective tissue and the on premises customer might be learning active directory with
...might be running other products from oracle often...ibm and maintain
...making sure that they can make their on premises system with
their clients system and as we've been doing this and building up...director...building
a service...the cloud...also notice that it's possible now thruster
...some essential identity management services through
...instead of the customer having...software on premises for it so
things like self-service password reset or self-service group management we can now
...in the cloud with our services running the...we can make those changes go
back on princess so now we have this connectivity which basically takes the
on premises directory and projects it into the cloud and also allows changes in
the...come back on premises it's really one logical directory between as
racconto...active directory so it's really just active directory
...question
...I...earlier was if you successfully are going to need...active directory was it turns out as
are active directory is active directory although if you...integrated with active directory and dyson
...too fast but you get...okay so
...integrating with...done in fact leasing customers more who
are pushing the responsibility for managing access to applications and doing
...management functions...see them pushing out more and more to
...clown sign of the equation because it's simply easier for them they don't have to the point
and premises software we do all the work of keeping the system running we
...all the work of adding...features they just have to go and
management from the cloud and they have to keep the connectivity between the cloud and on premises so it's a
very attractive proposition and we think
that we and this is the way we're driving this is the place we want you to be integrating applications?
So, it turns out as
...active directory is a very significant running service for microsoft already today
...identity management for more than five million organizations and we have more than
half-a-billion objects in this number goes up...rapidly
...sachin mentioned last week and earnings call that we have fifty million active
office the sixty-five users a month and all of those users...office
the sixty-five is using as...active directory as the way that they're signing and office...
sixty-five so there's fifty million acted users and on a given day we do between one
and two billion...and we expect that number...to continue going up
...going to get...and more so chances are if you're building a new
application...existing application you want to...organizations chances are
now organization or there's a good chance that organization already has answer active directory so if you can
provide this integration there's a number of these benefits that...you can get
a single sign on between obviously sixty-five, for example, in your application you can see
there directory...this and there's a bunch of other things in fact let's talk a little bit
beyond just being able and now integrate with enterprise identity management systems and
fulfill that request from your customers there's ways to answer active directory
and we can help you promote...application as well so when you
register your application without interactive directory...can't appear
...application gallery that we have today that people see
when administrator is...doing their centralize identity management as radiate
...seen as gallery today the gallery...it's probably difficult
thing in...the back of the room as more than twenty four hundred applications in it
I some of these are applications that developers like you of integrated with as...some of
...some of them are ones that microsoft has integrated...application menagerie
demeaned on and on the work that's a...these things together but in the gallery
...confine applications and very simply if you take a look.
At the one of the screen
you can the customer aren't who's looking at the gallant and initiate
the connection with your application right there within the gallery and literally they just
...up with you get information about them and there's no fancy set up, you know,
exactly what's going on because you're connected to the...
One thing that we're doing with the office teeing is there building a new office
store as well so if your customers and office
...sixty-five customer and the administrator spence part of their day in the
...obviously sixty-five management portal there will be a store where they can my applications
if you register an active directory your application will appear in the store and it
can be purchased amongst all these other applications that are...once
...customer decides...application requires it through the gallery or through
the store or even through a visiting your website and new initiating the
connection between answering the in your application the apple show up in their my apps
list so here's a user who uses office three sixty five and they've got
...sixty-five applications and more application there lerner if they
tenure application so...launcher.
Than when they have the they're everyday activity then do they're doing
...office three sixty five so if they're in...area...one
...or if they're in outlook and they click the waffle in the top
right hand corner then they'll see the applications that they've pinned
in your application can be right here and this can help promote user engagement they don't have to remember
where your applications to go back and visit...you can have that
exposure right there in the pan launcher so that they can keep coming back to it very easily?
So, those are some of the ways that.
We can help you...the application we can help you integrate
...enterprise identity management systems there's an awful lot that
we're doing as specialists in identity and communication also.
...the and the ability for us to protect these organizations that
...us with their identity management system so we have some
...security wanting that we're doing I'm going to show you a couple of these scenarios that we protect against
today there's others that we are talking about just yet and I
want to think about is your application has a way to sign people in that
you've built yourself when you ever...spend the time to invest in this sort of
monitoring we well but chances are unless you want to hire a whole bunch of people that are specialists
...management these are things that aren't going to get to the top of your stack
...as you're doing your work.
Of course all identity management systems provide ways to...the user tries event
password a number of times to do things like...them out but we also watch...the
...someone's trying that passwords...a very slow rate so they're trying to brute force
user very slow rate and what we do is we look to see if at any point they become...
If they actually ghastly user's password and we can look at
...look they're all these banks excellent...one this might be a successful
brute...past brute force classroom attack so we flagged that and we in signal
...another thing we do is we look for signing request that come from
...quotes dismisses places so if we have assigned...are coming from an online zer
...something like a tour then that might be someone is trying to attacking but
coverup their attack by coming through...we signal noses one.
We have a scenario this is the easiest one to explain it's just like if you've ever
gone on a trip and you use your credit card and your credit card was blocks because...that
...you're using a credit...placing hadn't been before in this case we look for
someone who sign in one location physical location and
sign in another physical location which is just suck geographically
...such then it's unlikely they actually made that...right so they signed in seattle
and they signed in south africa within five minutes
of each other chances are they didn't actually make that...so we can signal
...as a unlikely travel scenario in...the administrator.
Because our system is multi tenant we can also syntax that are
spanning the system so let's say that
...a bad guy out there and the bad guy is trying and passwords from a single
ip address across many different office three sixty-five tenants...can see that
...log and we can detect hey look this one ip addresses front all these different band-pass
...combinations across all these...we better
flag that as a problem...administrator and then finally within microsoft
minuteman working...now where we did we find we crackpot
...news about this...fairly regular basis we learn the ip addresses
of infected machines and we can share that information within microsoft so
from within our digital crimes unit to our signing systems so that we can
flag if we're seeing signing request coming from known infected devices ok so that's just
...few examples of ways that we provide protection
for users and these are things that we will continue to invest in because
we are building a expertise...were going to offer this identity
management systems capability these are things that it's probably not a good idea
for-you building your application to invest in it better if you can
simply take advantage of what we're doing so we can help you integrate with active directory we can help
...your application we can help you protector users.
And, we don't charge anything in factbecause of the amount of time that I
have for today's talk I had to take a couple of slides one of the things I want...dimension and I'll make and
...for the...answer active directory is absolutely free from basic
...services for basic directory serves as you can get when you're doing a development your
customers can gannett and they can use it with your application absolutely free now
...premium services...self-service password reset self-service group management and
such let me make available for...but the basic directory services and the basic
...services are available no charge me...protection services
are also available no charge but the reports than associated with them our part of the premium...
All right so how do you integrate...out how much is this how much inferences
...there's really three essential stacks and which
I'll demonstrate the first as and this is really
this is romantic really begins here you just need to...application with
...the once we know about it we can help matchmaking your application
with your customers we have to know some essential details we're going to give you a
client id is just like building a facebook application
...google application or dropbox application you need to go to their application consul you need to
...so that they know about you so we'll give you a client id we need to know
this thing called the redirect url this is the safe place for us to send tokens back
...when...in...you might have a secret for...on the
...of author doing I'll show that moment and then if you're going to call api
is from microsoft like if you're going to call the directory and you also need to declare those permissions
up-frontso,
once you've done that in your registered you add...to sign users in
an send signing...to answering machine the response
decoder response make sure came from manager ad get the information about the use around if you're going to call
and api that responsible also contain a thing called or
...code going-to-take that offloading you're...for tokens used to call
our api speed office api or the directory itself and then step
three you call those api...with those tokens...directory is just
arrest interface and...data ...interface you can call it to get information about users?
Now let me go through very quickly the essential protocol...the at runtime how
this works after you've registered and will show an example encode
...you're building a web app and you want to support as ready as way to sign-in and
a user and visiting your application are not...at all so they're?
It's...beginning from nowhere and they push a button on your apps and
...as an with...so you're going to sanding the signing
request to us via the user through of a three two and that's going to be
in the example I'm going to show later and open id connect
sign-in request and at that point the user has some interaction with us through the browser
...intern...in password and...and, finally there...and the result of that
sign-in is going to be of post back to your redirecting url with
a token representing the user which you're going to verify
the signature on and also that authorization code if you're going to be calling api
Once you will see that in make sure yes indeed this came from
...the new checked the signature on the talking with...key that...published in
...you can...you can now...your session with the customer
...because once browser so you're going to put...cooking down and now they're just talking you and you-know-who they
are now if you...call the api...take that authorization code and you
...token...point on answering...part of omar protocol and
open-ended connect protocols you takeauthorization...with your applications credentials...
redeem it for and...access token reference token the access tokens what you're going to
use to call the api and refreshed...you hang onto something get new
access opens if the...the access token that you have expires or if you want to
call different api without prompting...again refreshed open lets you
...a new access tokens almost like a influence perot's almost like a
...getting ticket and now you have the access token you can go ahead and you can call the
graphic you all right so let's take a look at this.
In demo form...they have to unlock my computer.
So, let's begin.
By looking at an application I previously registered.
Of course all of our several applications that we build...extremely simple absence
of to...app and you can actually get the code for this is in winded
...repo also that url again in a moment so you can find it when it's to nearly
...imagine which I small from the term touchy but I'd love to the
...or the short form fourteen...zoolander anybody
...failure anyway so there's a couple of this is...a
...eyal it was a really heavy sugary
dessert is a anyway I know identity's exciting...easier holds
...enthusiasm there's a couple things here that are important there's this
signing url this is neo relevant we're going to send the user to if the initiate own of that
...so if they if they click...button in the app onshore this is the...that we're going to
send them to so you need to provide...to...shows a logo selection
...the aperture this particular application is called a multi
tenant application because any tenant answer...sign in this...was a singleton
...application that only users in the tenet...was registered could accent that's if you're building
like a line-of-business out within a particular company and it's not for everybody else...just for your company but this one's
...here's the client id that's used in the code
and this apple also has a key because it's going to call the graphic api
and then finally...those to the...to redirected...registered for
this app one for the...that's running up in...websites and teeny
are not as websites net and then I have another one for my local debug that will show later these are
two locations where it's safe to send back and,
the response that includes the token for the user and such finally we see
this application asks for to permissions to call the
director itself the signing enable sign on and rename users profiles
one is the essential one that lets users sinus like the minimum you need to ask for
...as...integrated app unless you get...token for the user and look at the
...the users object specifically in the directory but nothing the
...that this the app also asks...directory data because it has a people pickering
going to show you how you can just browse users in the director if you need time and build a
...list to give people access to something, for example, so, this will also goes
...redid all right that's the...the app registration itself let's go
to the app I'll just refreshed really quickly and you'll notice that
there's two buttons here...added to the top of the template
...template one instance sign up for...organization up
...are the...which is just sign-in now the reason why I have this...in some of
...and administrator can sign up
...the application on behalf of the entire organization and in fact for
this particular application today it's necessary for an administrator to
sign up for this application because it once read directory...the
read directory permission that's their right now is very powerful allows the user to
you read the entire contents of the...and, put down so
...the administrator to say it's okayed is the sapped we have
some new permissions that are coming from the from the graph api where you'll be able to allow
...ordinary user to consent to see part of the directory enough to
...people...I they just didn't make it for this week it'll
probably be out next week in which case this will be a farmed that better demo next week
...unit ignite but anyway what I'm going to show right now is the administrators
signing up for the to do list application and, assign except
for my user can which is an way us...content and...
One...so I think is particularly interesting all scion.
So, I...to...now this is...this is the one-click that's going
to create federation between the two new application and the us
...tenet I have to consensus to this application being able to read directory data
enable sign-in okay I'm happy with that
I press exams and now any user in this
...tenet and sign in this application use it using their interactive directory
account there or if you like...obviously sixty-five identity there
...a microsoft...whatever happens to...the thing they were using before...using as
...active directory they can now use...this application let's quickly just I'll show you what
happens if we pick a different user and...instead of the administrator so we can show that they don't
have the experience for the consent.
Alternative user.
See there was no consent...login.
Ok, and, let's just take a quick work as well as the information that was
...about the alternative user to the app so there's some interesting stuff here this
is the immutable idea of the...they came from and measuring the
signify what organization there from this is the amenable idea of the user you can think of this like
a windows sand and safety use this id to
make security decisions about the user because this might be...but I can change
mining and, you know, this might be my first name last name here but these things
can easily change so they're not safe to make security decisions on because they're not
...say nine-year we can see that I authenticated with the password
...let's actually go into the interesting task part of the application and
...creates a task the finish build.
And, let's sharing this task with some other people who are going to
help me with when I share I can pick who I'm going to
share with and I can share with users in groups and this magnetic
field at the top is going to actually let me browse
the directory to pick who I want to share with before we once that was just get fiddler going in the
background and I'm going to touch this...field and immediately the and film
...javascript behind it that goes and does
...of indirectly and it just goes like una mention an address book just grab a bunch
...the first one to users in groups...directory...shown here let's go look at that
year and fiddler these options calls
...for the core support...here we go here is a?
...on...show.
Graft windows dot net that's the rest in point that you're going to
...to query the graph here's the tenant id of all
...montrose zone-dot-com and I'm just going to say give me the
for seven users...expo here says.
Give me the first seven groups and just will show them in that drop down
...something like...down to
try to find new people and we look at that then.
Here we have a more complex query.
So, I want to find users I want to find the first seven and I'm going
to send a filter find all of the
...since displaying starts...sq whose given name starts with
us too concerning search et cetera so I just I crafted...that query
in the javascript and cinepak respond to the...compost...dems
...of...which I can use to display disruptive solvable
...was share this task in-store great okay so that's a simple
...was to get the organization sign up to
use the application for other uses...for uses the for
use the graph let me sign-out and I'd like to show you a couple other things.
That swan...can do with this particular.
Application now one of the things that integrating with an enterprise identity
...system doesn't allows your application to in here some corporate
organizational policies with respect to what it takes to...application of your.
So,...this particular view is looking at the...tenants so I'm not looking at the application words
registered by the developer anymore this is where it has been consented to in
...swans also tenet the swans also administrator can see information
quincy.
If this were working information about the.
Well, you know, what?
Let's.
Let's start over with...income need a window.
And, we'll try to get...show this.
This requires multi factor authentication because if you
...talk last year I type...my password right into.
Right under the screen into the limbs forever
the recording and was one of my favorite passwords so
now it was a really good one...hand like lots of oper case lower-case nonsense
stuff and here we go I'm going to sign-in as.
The administrator now from this...is different in my...one user account which is actually also
administrator and let me go to the active directory portion of the
portal.
Okay, we're going to aggregate personal...known...this
...so tenant...look at applications.
...will find the to do...app there's a bunch of other apps
of course there and we can see information about the application but also.
We can control things like access rules to access this
...so application so let's see that I want to require multi factor authentication
just to visit...app and not for everybody let's say I'm going to pick a
group of users the engineering staff.
Needs to use multi factor authentication I could also do things like well the
engineering staff except users are in some group
...managed by the help-desk for people forgotten...phones and...and stuff like that
...can exceptions so...not a blanket and in this case
...in fact we can also do require multi factor unless the users on the corporate network
is a define some ip addresses but I'm not going to worry about that let's...on and
it save so now that authentication policies enforced against that's just that's in english.
If we go back to the today list application and I...to sign-in.
With mine's...swan account which is a part of the.
Is part of the engineering...now...factor authentication and
in fact it's a multi factor authentication using a mobile lapping of your...form?
And, I will check for an...authorization requests and
I'll verify yes this is different than the sm method...we have multiple methods for
authentication there we go so now I...now here's another scenario
...think about it for this particular case I...want any special
logic in the to newest application to handle this...multi factor...that
was all...wires...nothing happened in the apps code now let's imagine even more complex
scenario imagine your customer...to antonia thing you think this can happen your customer
...as noone I've decided since your applications so important and contains
information so critical my business that I want you to prevent people with jill
whalen consumes from accessing...on europe imagine what you would add bengal
...am I going to implement that well with what we know
...as radiate and integration with in soon we actually make a possible and
we're working on this to saying yeah,
and, you can get to that application unless you're coming from a nonzero broken phone
...been protected that has encryption
...on it and other rules that are related to the device health and device identity and
...administrator will be able to configure those things and you won't have to write any code to
...if you let your users sign-in when as your ad.
All right let's do one more thing let's actually look at the application
so here I have the tireless reinvention app...nbc application
it users...the...win model for handling
its authentication so there's only middleware...we produce that does open id connect
...center let's find out of that actually works on a start the app and sense of
...points in interesting places.
As it...up mission ok so here's the first-placethat we
...a startup class over here.
...very...screen very difficult fantasy and then startup classes...initialize the owen
pipeline and this...your configure office going-to initiate the authentication part of
the pipeline it's been a load the open-eyed connect and some other middleware...continue will
...that happens that happens in this file near called starting off which is
...especially in file that you create and here's the configure author routine
...the configure offer...these first two lines get the hooking middleware
set up so this middleware handles nys session with the users browser after the
sign-in and then a little bit further down here we
initialize the open id connect middleware that you can get from us and
...of the essential lines are giving a client id
...from that registration in here we put it in the web...of...to
initialized middleware the authority is the location of
...ad for most people this is going to be loggingwindows online dot com
but, there's actually multiple instances of answer ad in the world...depending on
how many instances individual instances of windows act of microsoft agile that we've
...so there's one, for example, in china...we have the public installation
...but mostly this...dot microsoft online dot com and the tenant
your connecting to or if you don't know the tenant there's a special because it's a multi
ten application is a special authority called common that you're going to send the user
to and then furthermore we're going to catch some processing notifications
that can happen one of the key notifications is I received
...authorization...remembers part of the assigning dance.
We're going to receive...token about the user that receives token is going to be grabbed
by the middleware the...going to make sure it was signed by the right a by answering in the middle...going-to-take the
information about the user out and put it into your application as a set of claims and
it also receive...authorization code this next set
of code here takes that authorization code and uses a library that
we've created called the as the active directory authentication library or
...and it returns the authorization code into
...access soaking refresh open and caches goals
...all of the lifecycle of those so once you've done this dance
the particular interesting line here is acquire token...authorization code after you
centering up now you're talking you're application has a...for this user
that you can ask for later by calling acquire tokens so you can call the graphic...call the office
...sixty-five api oreoand,...has the refresh open-ended takes care of all
the logic for a using with first tokens to get new access tokens when the
expire etc so you don't have to worry about taking care of that yourself
managing all of that authentication state yourself will do for you in this library.
Let's continue and...finally put
...back on the application let's...code behind the...buttons
...press sign-in there's an account controller here
the account controller has the code for behind that scion button and it's this
...code here which since the openly connects
...request a...authentication challenge and the
...automatically process the response when it comes back because the middleware in the
...ahead of the application will just continue their.
And, now the options center...as rainy...but sign user
in let's go to fiddler again we'll take a look here's the call.
And, in fact I've exploded this out just for time.
It's a remember we call the authorization endpoint
...using common because there's a multi...application and
here's the rest of the request the client idea of the application the response
...means I want the results return to me as a form...
I would like and authorization code and ninety token authorization codes
...colleague...the id tokens...user is this is straight up open aidid connect which means I
want ninety connect I...users information in the id token
the state traps information for the application about where descent that the
...back later it's like
...paints nato please make sure is...me in our case we...we
trap information about where to put these are back in the application...the so think
it's a...button on this particular page please bring them back to the page and then finally the
redirected ori then it's safe to send that token back to in this case you can see
...local host account
sign-in that falls within the redirect url...the application in the direct.
So, that's.
A simple demo.
Of integrating with
...if you go to get hans last one and you can find the repo
web group...dot net it's a forked of a basic sample that we have that shows you how to use
great plains and you can go ahead and do
whatever you want with this particular piece of code...seeing...how much of this we can backpack
...standard samples by compare this one specially?
Now...a very simple case where...and...signing
...app but there's a lot more things that people do
applications today than just bellwether...pc...you've got mobile apps and
...was designed to help you with all of the different apologies that are involved to make
is applications work so we have...typical...I like call this the
...inanimate and water not application...one more
...in...web api when api...pc mobile apps
or if you have people just calling you from demons or server...and how do you authenticate
...when api and often...more of a
...of the applications dropping...the when app into the when api because
...the action what you want have all the action having in one place so the web
...simply becoming a presentation layer for the people using browsers
and it's calling the web api and how do you do authentication from the went out to the
when api from the mobile...the...the web api from one
...api to another and, incorporate example docking
sign has assigning app on ios where
the mobile app talks to the docket sign api
...when api in the darkest...api talks to sharepoint to pick up a document
assignment and...put it back how do you preserve the
users identity all the way through that because when you arrived sharepoint you have to have the
users real identity right you can't you can't just...sign saying well I
wanna-be this user now they actually has to be user that is a legitimate one is
already signing...the way that we handle all of these scenarios...the way we
handle the fact that it could be a
ios app android app it could be browsers on a wide variety platforms you
might be writing your server code in dot net or in...
ass or java how do we make this all works well we decided to support a
set of standard protocols and emily when you look at this diagram
...it boils down to...are strategic protocols are all
through and open-eyed knickknacks it turns out
...connect is merely a lol and xtwo layer if you will and extension upon off
to all so that's where we're making most our investment were doing that because these
protocols are really friendly across all these different platforms their relatively straightforward
employment if you have...http stack you can do a little bit of crypto and you
can serialized jayson then you can handle these protocols so it makes
possible across all these apps we also support dummies federation salmon as ways to
sign...because the popularity of those protocols days...already
...application arnie sports same...because of the demand to
federated connect with enterprise identity system so we support sample as well
...this is basically our strategic approach on how we do this and there are samples and show you how
to do every single one of these scenariosin our developer
...in our developer guide...can
...you can compose them together so you can create this entire topology if you wanted to?
...talk a little bit about the graphic api
...just a touch a few more elements here so of course you can
get users groups devices...objects and
rancor you can see relationships so you can see the organizational hierarchy the same way
...say inside and...outlook or something...
the relationships between users in the organizational hierarchy is also there it's just plain all
...use the usual...mechanisms to calling impact
...xml we prefer you call-in and get back jason and.
We support...as you saw so you can make these calls lengthen javascript running
and running in your web app running in the browser its own...
Compatible and we're close to adding or data...for compatibility as well as a
...helper libraries if you don't want to make the rest calls directly but you're welcome to make a
...it's just a simple we havelibrary center for
...iowa's android right now and we're working on warm
there's interactive reference to show you all the different api is what
...a particular request looks like and what the response looks like that's available
...msdn...also find that links more developer guide which I'll talk about...we get to the end?
The...library is something that we put a considerable amount of
investment into because while for the graphics just rest calls no big deal go ahead and do
...when it comes to getting the authentication protocol
...while is straightforward we don't think it's worth your time to
reproduce this code or you might need security mistakes...the code so we dowe
...create...libraries...for...so you didn't have to figure out
itself and we do encourage you to use these libraries be the media library on the
client...or things like the only library the node chance libraries that
...on server-side
...all open-source you're welcome to contribute back we love it when
people contribute back or you can...you can suck me
the whole source and your application you're welcome to do all of those things and we are
working more languages so we do get requests for python you get requests
...ruby...and we need to expand on our server-side we need to expand
our support for things like java and there's not there's not enough there right now and we're working on a?
Ok, futures fifteen
...fly through assign a set of the things that we're working on
...by no means represent all the things we're working on
...these are some interesting ones when it comes to identity
an important aspect of identity's always keys
and team management we recently put into preview a capability that we call key...is
designed when at least the initial preview of cable was designed...a couple of course narrows and
...one is helping you get your secrets away from deadlocks
...storage keys in a storage
...are in your source code today man a lot of people can be
...those keys I don't remember I remember reading this blog article the fellow
wrote as unrelated to answer indeed but he was doing some.
Prototyping I think and ruby and nature of the put is
...code into...organization...
realized I forgot I have one amazon sthree keys in my source code
undertaken within five minutes you take them out and he went to bed...look at the next morning at a
...several text warnings from...a phone call that has a
...run-up twenty five hundred-dollars and charges because there are people who have robots that
watch...hub for the checking of things that look like keys and then they take them
...so we want to get these...out of sources much as possible
what is a safe place to put keys a specifically auditor and
...place to put keys and the way that you get the key is one of the...is
by authenticate intuit with answering theanother thing another key scenario for
key scenario for...is to allow customers to bring their own
...and this is something as you get bigger and more successful enterprise customers
...and they're going to say things like...reasons I need to be in control of the encryption
keys the new used to encrypt my
...in your application it's not going to work for me if you tell me its
...with yorkies I have to control those keys so let's go through
...scenarios for...explains it so
then it comes to life the first is I want to get my secrets...my
...semi storage...and the way this works is use the developer
...key malt and you put your storage...this can just be, you know, as a small number of people your team
...came up with a storage skis into good then you go register your application
esri these so it has an identity and along with that identity we're going to
...it a credential which is a certificate new upload that certificate answering
the engineer asher project and then you can throw away the...file you don't need to a
...the private key and now...grant application access to those
...in the cable and...your app wakes up and asks workload influential
ad and sense that token...key...and infectious back all of the storage
...and it uses...the storage...are no longer...
And, the key its use minute by the application authenticate...the
...is...known on your...right and now you can runand,
this is spontaneous applies one...fantastic thank you
...hard on this one now we did we actually work really hard on this one the another
example...bring your own key examples work we're doing with office me...what make all the advanced encryption
...and this is a case where the customer sense only
...office three sixty five igni all of the mailbox data encrypted to
...that I on whether this is going to work is the customer goals and
...the context of your application so I go to the customer
...creates a cable and uploads encryption...the cable and asymmetric
encryption the customer has...choice with our system to have that stored
...protecting software or even in a harbors...module so once we decide...the
...hardware security module and then the only grant exchange which has an
identity answer directly the ability to use that to
exchange then goes and...some one or more encryption case that is can use to
encrypt mailbox data and...one by one sentence
...chemo incense...this key forming
...gets back a bunch of stay with me here encrypted encryption
keys which is storms ok so now it has encrypted mailbox
...and encrypted keys everything's encrypted when it wakes up and
...work on a mailbox it takes the encrypted encryption key sends...the key
...against...by the key...all comes back to exchange
...work on the mailbox this chain of prosper the
...is suitable dissatisfied the compliance requirements of many customers and
issuing about...is well if you have similar scenarios okay that's...
As...active directory is identity management is a service for organizations...one
Might your company and helps with identity management free
...employees but there's more that we can do here we can
provide identity management services that work for an application that also faces
...to customers and we call this answering
the bing to see...simply taking as rainy as an
...adding features to it so we...all the goodness of
a parkinson's twenty-eight datacenters and...that has datacenter fail over the
...between...and has the intrusion detection
...monitoring capabilities we take all of that and we answer the ability to
...with social ideas the ability to sign-in with
...what we call application local user accounts so you have user councilor
gist for your application that are stored as rainy we take care of helping
users sign up...in reset
their passwords change their profiles and you do all of this
...for your applications...just like your application and using the programming model I
talked earlier no difference in the programming model it's just
...with some more features now this one's not...have a free level to
...to a certain number of users and authentication but beyond that
...be consumption of pricing so that we get paid fairly for the amount of the
system you use based on the number of users and put in a number of authentication
...month that you do I promise you...where to find this very
affordable...people that we talked to already because we can take advantage of this huge scale we are
the app people in...talk to take a look at what they're doing today to handle customs the consumer
...signing and how much it would cost...use our stuff plus all of
the security benefits and everything that you get from it and it's a it's a pretty compelling
proposition this is in work right nowlet me show you an example fictional
contents of airlines wants to build a checking system for their
...on one side we've got a customize...page on the other side customize sign up
page...can see that there's multiple accounts for the application those are all
...ad...we provide ways for users to recent...password etc on the
sign of side we can help you gather information from the user when they sign
up including arbitrary extended information that you define white frequent flyer...
will gather that information...the directory will let you query into the graphic api will be able
...tokens when the user signs into your application...
...are working hard on this will be in pretty soon.
Another thing that we're working on is there's a lot of applications out there that would like to
sign users in both with microsoft
accounts and menagerie the accounts but today you have to do
to pieces of work so we're going to blend these together so
...one in point he'll be able to visit you'll be able to send users their with co-author
...connect requests when they arrive they'll have one sign
...we'll take care of figuring out...with our consumer identity or the signing
their work identity will sort all that we'll get back response and,
I'll tell you where they came from but you'll just have one
...kale one point that you need to do...you need to use to get
uses across all of this at the same time we're taking this opportunity to build
a new registration carnal for how you register your
application us and take this out of the actual portal cone
...answer subscription to get to this portal going-to-take everything that we've learned about how to
streamline...and...in there so
that will be a simpler way to get your application registered to work with either microsoft account
for answer active directory the...today or this
week and build the office team is also talking about how they're taking their api
...for consumer one driver examples of the consumer files api
...files api consumer calendar and email api the business
calendar and email api and...unifying notes so now you'll be able to
senior user...in and then you'll be able to connect to their calendar and you
won't have to have logic to figure out wall which...take is this a user
microsoft counters and...ad account is...there you know,...corporate one
...consumer one drive in all just be one thing you have to do.
...one up there.
Let's take a look at what this will look,
like so I have the fictional fabric encounter application and the
users been...unifying point assign n and if...enters
...work address then...her work sign-in page.
You'll see her work sign-in page and on signals from there is
...were to show up and enter hermicrosoft account
...outlook dot com then we detect that...well on the...page and we
send her through to the microsoft account sign-in page.
And, finally if at some point she use fabric encounter with both
...consumer and business identity's at some point you might return
...up all the different choices that she has so she can decide what do I want to sign with
my work identity or do I want to...with my consumer identity and
will further blending simplify the...experience more and more
what-you sar right now is the big beginning this will be in preview also very soon?
Finally we're also doing work on the device sign
...the equation and you might have heard with windows ten similar to windows
...windows eight with your consumer identity you'll be able
...windows ten with your work identity through answer ad join and once
...join your desktop to...ad through this process...single sign on to
...based on premises resources you'll get single science
a native applications that use...account manager api
...want to learn more about this arbitrary is going to talk about it in his session later this
week on friday and then finally web apps...use as...for sign-in
...also get automatic single...so I can walk up...windows desktop
...my windows desktop if I were...to the to do list application press sign-in
...I don't have to enter my name and password or do anything because I'm already sign in windows?
Also samoa.
We're doing similar work on
...devices so-if you have multiple applications on your
iowa's device that all use as...it can be a real pain in the but to have to
...song...word or something and at assigning with my corporate name
...this tiny ...putting my long my sixteen character corporate password into
...your mobile application and I have to do the same thing that's not a good user
experience or building authentication broker applications that we put on
...android that if you use the...pri
...your application when the user goes to sign-in they'll be switched over to the broker
...and we can use an account they've already signed in
...because the broker will remember about the user...it's also
...system that will use to have put the device identity into the equation
when the user signing...we can do things like that joe break detection
through into or if the user has encrypted advice...routines examine
health state advice management state...the device through the broker applications this
at is going to come in the form of our authenticate
...we have today for multi faq roth...going to grow into having
these broker capabilities so that your applications using arresting case
...better experience or mobile devices as well.
Ok, so, if you would like to get started very simple.
You're going to mean answer so,
you can answer ad if...you already have...sixty-five or you already have
...already have answer ad and you can do experiments with that just go to the
...portal financial active directory section today just this morning
we published a new developer guide that has a series of new stuff
in it like getting started topics if you want to know right now how to build
...application or android application or a nbc.
Or javascript web application there are topics now you can go to intel's you
...is here's the important things...need to know about building this application step-by-step to
find that developer guide you go to actually I think it the
linking can actually find the length of the as well right now we're working on
getting that fuse together but if you go to the link that's on the screen here
you can find out developer guide and we'll make sure that you can get to it from...documentation
...access management active directory develop just remember that
...simple this remember that and then eventually it'll...in the search rankings as
...goaded both on stocks...to have you...us
talk we...every new feature that we do on our team blog if you can't remember
the address just...active directory...blog google
...it's always the top one...always be able to find it and we facts.
Remember you are going to be successful.
And, if...successful burundi asked...and enterprise identity management
...weights do it now integrate with abstracted directory
...simple becomes...tremendous benefits for your customer
from their user experience for you and the ability to promote your application get people signed up
that people...key people engage and
newman love to hampshire this is a big deal for us and it's all
...on...protocols and open-source and within thank...
The ticker sense that I have five four three two one
minute left I'll take questions in the expert area
there's an...media experts...over there right now so if you'd like to meet with me or
...and ask questions we happened to...for-you thank you.